[
  { "question": "X + 4 = 10", "wrongAnswers": [5, 7, 4], "rightAns": [6] },
  { "question": "X + 10 = 15", "wrongAnswers": [8, 4, 6], "rightAns": [5] },
  { "question": "9 - X = 6", "wrongAnswers": [4, 8, 2], "rightAns": [3] },
  { "question": "8 - X = 5", "wrongAnswers": [4, 2, 5], "rightAns": [3] },
  { "question": "3 * X = 9", "wrongAnswers": [7, 1, 6], "rightAns": [3] },
  { "question": "X * 5 = 10", "wrongAnswers": [5, 1, 6], "rightAns": [2] },
  { "question": "6 / X = 2", "wrongAnswers": [9, 6, 2], "rightAns": [3] },
  { "question": "X / 1 = 4", "wrongAnswers": [6, 3, 2], "rightAns": [4] },
  { "question": "X * 1 = 7", "wrongAnswers": [9, 8, 6], "rightAns": [7] },
  { "question": "8 / X = 2", "wrongAnswers": [2, 7, 6], "rightAns": [4] }
]
